<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TruthorErrCapstone</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_menu">MainMenuActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>


    <string-array name="correctAnswerNumbers">
        <item>Select Correct Answer</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="categoriesList">
        <item>Select Category</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="faqText">Welcome to the FAQs for the Truth or Err app! Below you\'ll find answers to some common questions regarding login, password changes, profile, and general information about the app.\n\n
        <b><u>Login Questions:</u></b>\n\n

Q: How do I log in to the Truth or Err app?\n
A: To log in, simply open the app and enter your registered email and password on the login page.\n\n

Q: What do I do if I can\'t remember my password?\n
A: You can reset your password by clicking on the "Forgot Password" link on the settings page under Account. Follow the instructions to reset your password.\n\n

Q: Can I change my login email?\n
A: Yes, you can change your email by contacting our support team through the app\'s Help page in settings.\n\n

        <b><u>Password Changes:</u></b>\n\n

Q: How do I change my password?\n
A: To change your password, go to your account settings and click on the "Change Password" button. Enter your current password, then your new password, and confirm the new password.\n\n

Q: How often should I change my password?\n
A: We recommend changing your password every three months for security reasons.\n\n

Q: What are the password requirements?\n
A: Your password must be at least eight characters long and contain at least one uppercase letter, one lowercase letter, one number, and one special character.\n\n

        <b><u>About Truth or Err App:</u></b>\n\n

Q: What is Truth or Err app?\n
A: Truth or Err is a fun and engaging app that lets you test your knowledge on a variety of topics. You can choose from different categories such as history, science, pop culture, and more.\n\n

Q: Is the Truth or Err app free?\n
A: Yes, the app is free to download and use.\n\n

Q: Can I play the Truth or Err app with friends?\n
A: Yes, you can play the app with friends by adding friends, sending friend requests, and challenging your friends as well.\n\n
Q: Is there a limit to the number of friends I can add?\n
A: No, there is no limit to the number of friends you can add to the app.\n\n

        <b><u>Deleting Your Account:</u></b>\n\n

Q: How do I delete my Truth or Err account?\n
A: To delete your account, go to your profile page and click on the "Delete Account" button. You will then be asked to confirm the deletion.\n\n

Q: Will deleting my account delete all my data?\n
A: Yes, deleting your account will delete all your data, including your score, history, and friend list.\n\n

Q: Can I recover my account after deleting it?\n
A: No, once you delete your account, it cannot be recovered.\n\n
We hope these answers have been helpful! If you have any other questions or concerns, please contact our support team through the app\'s Help page found under settings.\n
    </string>
</resources>